hi everyone rey here on this video i am
going to talk about money life i funds
this is under the manulife asset
management trust corporation which is a
subsidiary of manulife philippines so we
are not going to talk about manulife
philippines insurances we are going to
talk about the investments and the uitf
funds that you can invest in
[Music]
the manulife trust suite was launched in
september 2017 and currently we have a
total of 16 funds three funds are
onshore and 13 funds are offshore what's
good in this company is that in the
philippines it is the only one that
offers both peso or dollar offshore
classes in all of its offshore funds i'm
going to give you an overview of the
website wherein you can invest in the
different types of funds in the company
okay so the website is manulifeim.com.ph
so here it is and let's go to our funds
okay so i want to show you the different
types of funds that we have let's go
here in unit investment trust fund and
you can see
we have the 16 funds manulife american
growth equity feeder fund to know about
what a feeder fund and
fund of funds is you can check the
separate video that i made okay so
this fund for example american growth
fund is a type of fund that is invested
in u.s stocks okay so you can click on
the brochure and you can see the risk
assessment it is an aggressive type of
fund
you can
um invest in either u.s dollar or peso
equity feeder fund
so meaning it's invested stocks in
equities
and the minimum amount minimum initial
investment is 100
or 5 000 pesos
minimum succeeding transaction amount
meaning when you add additional money to
your investment it should either be 100
or 5000 pesos minimum holding period is
30 days so you should leave your money
in the fund for at least 30 days
we have a trust fee of 1.75
per annum risk classification is
aggressive early redemption charge is
one percent meaning if you
redeem your investment or pull out your
investment in less than 30 days or less
than the minimum holding period then you
get charged one percent so the target
fund is the manulife global fund or u.s
equity fund again you can learn about
the target fund on this separate video i
made
um the benchmark is snp 500 index and
the target fund investment manager is
money life investment
management usnse okay so basically all
these fonts have this type of summary
when you open the brochure and
um you can see where the fund is
invested in so it says here it is
invested in north american companies
and
it explains here why this fund of course
access to the u.s market and
yeah so you can review all these details
about each of the funds that the company
offers
here we have manual life asia best
select equity fund
similar to the first fund it um
gives you a summary of what it's all
about
this is invested in also equities um
it's invested in companies under
countries under the asia pacific
okay
so here you can also see reits
fund of funds again fund of funds is
discussed on a separate video
so
these are invested on reads in different
asian countries as well under the asia
pacific
these funds allow us to diversify our
portfolio in to
offshore classes so this isn't just in
the philippines you can invest through
peso in different countries
so manulife drug and growth equity
feeder fund is focused more on like
chinese companies
wealth fund is also invested in stocks
okay but this is actually um peso
denominated this is one of the three
funds that is invested on shore in
so this one is um
philippine peso only
and
this is invested in companies under the
philippine stock exchange
okay my new life global health care
equity fund so invested in companies
related to healthcare
global read feeder fund this is invested
in reits in other countries not just in
the philippines i've made a separate
video of this money life global
technology equity feeder fund invested
in companies under the technology sector
okay
manulife global thematic opportunities
equity feeder fund money life india
equity feeder fund
so
invested in indian companies
global multi-asset diversified income
fund global preferred income fund so you
can also see
here
that
um compared to the other
brochures you can see one additional
here
unit income distribution frequency
is semi-annually okay so yeah i'm gonna
talk about the in campaign fund later
okay
no let me discuss it now so when you see
this unit income distribution frequency
it means that it is an in campaign fund
and an income paying fund is a fund that
gives you payout periodically it depends
on the type of fund so on this case
your regular payout is being released
semi-annually okay so twice a year
usually this also applies to reits so
reits are also in campaign funds my new
life stable income fund is also one of
the three onshore funds this is a bond
fund
as you can see here a bond fund so the
risk appetite is not as aggressive as
the other funds that is invested in
equities
okay and also manulife money market fund
okay this is also the third
onshore fund
okay so once you've decided on what type
of fund you'd like to invest in actually
you can also
compare funds
okay so let's say
i'd like to compare manulife american
growth
equity feeder fund
let's see
see um
philippine peso and philippine peso
and
let's try the asia pacific read fund of
funds
okay so you can compare these two funds
you can actually add one more let's say
my new life equity
dragon growth let's say dragon growth
active eater fund
here you can see the historical data of
the funds you can compare it one year
three years
since it was launched
year-to-date
okay so this will help you choose what
type of fund to invest in you can also
see the date you can also choose the
date
generally the economy is really low
um with you know everything going on in
the world it's generally low not just in
this this types of fun but in different
types of funds and platforms as well so
yeah you can compare the funds here
and
basically that's it if you're interested
to invest in these types of funds you
may do so by contacting me actually you
can go to contact us fill up the form
and wait for a wealth specialist to
contact you but if you want to skip that
you can just contact me directly i'm
going to leave my details below because
i myself i'm a licensed wealth
specialist in man united philippines and
i'd be glad to help you out if you'd
like to diversify your portfolio and
invest in different types of funds
especially offshore funds like out of
the philippines funds you can consider
investing through manulife iphones
so that's it guys i hope you enjoyed
watching my video i hope you learned
something let me know if i missed
anything or if you have any questions
please comment down below don't forget
to subscribe and hit the like button and
the notification bell in order to be
notified for more videos similar to
these thank you bye
i myself i'm a wealth spelled chalice
i myself i'm a wealth specialist
[Music]
you